{
  "problem1": {
    "problem": "23 + 45",
    "answer": 68
  },
  "problem2": {
    "problem": "67 - 29",
    "answer": 38
  },
  "problem3": {
    "problem": "8 * 7",
    "answer": 56
  },
  "problem4": {
    "problem": "84 / 12",
    "answer": 7
  },
  "problem5": {
    "problem": "56 + 37",
    "answer": 93
  },
  "problem6": {
    "problem": "91 - 48",
    "answer": 43
  },
  "problem7": {
    "problem": "9 * 6",
    "answer": 54
  },
  "problem8": {
    "problem": "72 / 8",
    "answer": 9
  },
  "problem9": {
    "problem": "34 + 28",
    "answer": 62
  },
  "problem10": {
    "problem": "85 - 39",
    "answer": 46
  },
  "problem11": {
    "problem": "7 * 8",
    "answer": 56
  },
  "problem12": {
    "problem": "63 / 9",
    "answer": 7
  },
  "problem13": {
    "problem": "19 + 46",
    "answer": 65
  },
  "problem14": {
    "problem": "73 - 55",
    "answer": 18
  },
  "problem15": {
    "problem": "12 * 5",
    "answer": 60
  },
  "problem16": {
    "problem": "96 / 16",
    "answer": 6
  },
  "problem17": {
    "problem": "27 + 38",
    "answer": 65
  },
  "problem18": {
    "problem": "42 - 67",
    "answer": -25
  },
  "problem19": {
    "problem": "11 * 9",
    "answer": 99
  },
  "problem20": {
    "problem": "88 / 11",
    "answer": 8
  },
  "problem21": {
    "problem": "53 + 29",
    "answer": 82
  },
  "problem22": {
    "problem": "31 - 58",
    "answer": -27
  },
  "problem23": {
    "problem": "6 * 13",
    "answer": 78
  },
  "problem24": {
    "problem": "75 / 15",
    "answer": 5
  },
  "problem25": {
    "problem": "44 + 36",
    "answer": 80
  }
}
